For a list of all the json files that NBA releases for each day:

http://data.nba.net/10s/prod/v1/...

This list will provide links to other relevant information including:

scores and stats for games of the day: http://data.nba.net/10s/prod/v1/...

player information: http://data.nba.net/10s/prod/v1/...

all star roster (for this weekend): http://data.nba.net/10s/prod/v1/...

player profile: (note: you need to look up the player id in order to get the player’s stat)

/data/10s/prod/v1/2016/players/{{personId}}_profile.json

and more including team rosters, schedules, standings, etc.

============================

Just answering this old thread can be installed without pip On windows or Linux:

1) Download Requests from https://github.com/kennethreitz/requests click on clone or download button

2) Unzip the files in your python directory .Exp your python is installed in C:Python\Python.exe then unzip there

3) Depending on the Os run the following command:

Windows use command cd to your python directory location then setup.py install
Linux command: python setup.py install
